You came to your Nanodegree program to learn.
لقد جئتم إلى برنامج Nanodegree من أجل التعلم.
So we want to make sure you do as much of that as possible.
لذا ينبغي التأكد من ذلك بأقصى قدر ممكن.
You learn when you grapple with tough problems,
إنكم تتعلمون عندما تواجهون المشكلات الصعبة،
when you stretch your brain to new limits.
وعندما توسعون مدارككم إلى حدود جديدة.
To make this happen, it's crucial for you to work on your projects yourself,
ولتحقيق ذلك، فمن المهم جدًا أن تعملوا على مشروعاتكم بأنفسكم،
since that's how you'll hone your skills.
لأن هذه هي الطريقة التي تمكنكم من تحسين مهاراتكم.
Throughout your Nanodegree program,
خلال برنامج Nanodegree،
we'll encourage you to share what you've created with your community and
سنشجعكم على مشاركة ما قمتم بإنشائه مع المجتمع
you'll have the chance to see what your peers have worked on as well.
وستتاح لكم الفرصة لمعرفة ما قام به زملاؤكم أيضًا.
But please be mindful of how other people's work influences your projects.
لكن يُرجى مراعاة كيفية تأثير عمل الآخرين على مشروعاتكم.
Using more than a small part of work that is not your own
فإن استخدام جزء صغير من عمل ليس عملكم
goes beyond the bounds of authentic learning.
يتجاوز حدود التعلم الأصيل.
Keep in mind what your goals are, to be able to use the skills and
يجب أن تضعوا أهدافكم نصب أعينكم لتكونوا قادرين على استخدام المهارات
knowledge you're developing in the real world.
والمعرفة التي تقومون بتطويرها في العالم الحقيقي.
Let's make sure you get there.
دعونا نتأكد من أنكم تفهمون بشكل صحيح.